Steady!
꾸준한!
Here. Here it comes. Here... Come on. Come on, little guy!
여기요. 여기 온다. 여기... 어서. 어서, 꼬마야!
My love, you gotta eat. The day is only halfway over.
내 사랑, 밥을 먹어야 해요. 하루가 이제 절반밖에 남지 않았습니다.
Your brain needs food to run.
뇌가 작동하려면 음식이 필요합니다.
I'm not really hungry.
별로 배가 고프지 않아요.
Oh, you're not?
아, 그렇지 않나요?
Well, why don't you ask your GHSR1a receptors?
글쎄, 물어보는 게 어때? 당신의 GHSR1a 수용체는요?
I'm certain they'd tell you a different story.
그들이 당신에게 말할 거라고 확신해요 다른 이야기.
Anywhoozle, I was thinking,
누구든지, 내 생각엔,
how would you like to have your new friends over sometime?
당신은 어떻게 하시겠습니까? 언제 새로운 친구를 만나러 갈까?
We could make a bonfire.
우리는 모닥불을 피울 수 있어요.
Hey, Mom, how much longer are we sticking around for?
엄마, 얼마나 더 기다리세요? 우리 계속 붙어 있는 거야?
Well, let me see.
글쎄요.
I have a faculty meeting at 2:00, and then I have--
2시에 교수회의가 있어요. 그리고 난--
I mean sticking around in Hawkins.
내 말은 호킨스에 머물고 있다는 뜻이에요.
Whoa! Where is this coming from?
와! 이건 어디서 나오는 걸까요?
Watch, watch, watch, watch! Careful, careful!
봐, 봐, 봐, 봐! 조심해, 조심해!
Oops! Uh-oh!
이런! 어-오!
Captain Lab Safety to the rescue.
Captain Lab Safety가 구조를 요청합니다.
Hey, what's up, D Man?
안녕, 무슨 일이야, D맨?
Hi, Daniel.
안녕, 다니엘.
I come bearing sandwiches.
나는 샌드위치를 ​​들고 온다.
Someone grabbed the wrong backpack again.
누군가 또 다른 배낭을 움켜쥐었습니다.
Thank you. I'm Starvin' Marvin over here.
감사합니다. 저는 여기 Starvin' Marvin입니다.
But the brain needs food to run.
하지만 뇌가 작동하려면 음식이 필요합니다.
You know, I thought you liked it here.
있잖아, 난 네가 여기가 마음에 든다고 생각했어.
I can't remember the last time you had friends over.
기억이 나지 않아요 지난번에 친구를 만났을 때.
Honey.
꿀.
I can't leave Hawkins. I...
나는 호킨스를 떠날 수 없다. 나는...
Just not yet.
아직은 아닙니다.
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Who's leaving Hawkins?
워, 워, 워! 호킨스를 떠나는 사람은 누구입니까?
I've made too much progress in my work to give up now.
내 일이 너무 많이 진전됐어 지금 포기하려고.
Your mother is close to a real breakthrough.
네 엄마는 가까이 계시지 진정한 돌파구를 마련합니다.
One day, people will be able to revive their rotting produce
언젠가는 사람들이 할 수 있을 것이다. 썩어가는 농산물을 되살리기 위해
because of your mom's work.
엄마 일 때문에.
She could change the world if she sticks with it.
그녀는 세상을 바꿀 수 있다 그녀가 그것을 고수한다면.
Fine. Whatever. I get it.
괜찮은. 무엇이든. 알겠습니다.
Just give me a heads-up when you're done "changing the world"
미리 알림을 주세요 "세상을 바꾸는 것"이 끝나면
so I can start packing, okay?
그럼 짐 싸기 시작해도 돼, 알았지?
Nikki. Nikki.
니키. 니키.
- No. - Who wants my PB&J?
- 아니. - 누가 내 PB&J를 원하는가?
I got apple juice!
사과주스를 받았어요!
Hey, you know you really came through for me yesterday.
이봐, 너도 알지? 당신은 어제 나에게 정말로 와줬어요.
And none of it would have been possible without the Hawkins Investigators Club.
그리고 그 어느 것도 가능하지 않았을 거야 호킨스 수사관 클럽 없이.
No way! This is awesome!
안 돼요! 정말 대단해요!
Thanks, everybody. I humbly accept this very cool hat.
고마워요, 여러분. 나는 이 멋진 모자를 겸손히 받아들인다.
All right, now before we declare the H.I.C. a definitive success,
알았어, 이제 선언하기 전에 H.I.C. 확실한 성공이네요
let's double-check our math. Start us off, Will.
수학을 다시 확인해 봅시다. 시작해 보세요, 윌.
Well, we discovered that if the spores don't find a host within 12 hours,
음, 우리는 포자가 12시간 이내에 호스트를 찾지 못해
they die permanently.
그들은 영원히 죽습니다.
And it's now been more than 24 hours since the last incident.
그리고 이제 24시간 이상이 지났습니다 지난 사건 이후로요.
So we should be in the clear.
그러므로 우리는 분명해야 합니다.
Although, we never did get to the bottom of Charlie's red light.
하지만 우리는 결코 바닥에 도달하지 못했습니다 찰리의 빨간불.
Take the win, Dustin!
승리하세요, 더스틴!
The final test is right here.
마지막 테스트가 바로 여기에 있습니다.
The last of our H.I.C. tip boxes.
우리 H.I.C.의 마지막 팁 상자.
If we open it and find a clue, there's still work to do.
열어서 단서를 찾으면, 아직 할 일이 남아 있어요.
If we don't,
그렇지 않으면
that means the Hawkins Investigators Club has succeeded.
그건 호킨스 수사관 클럽을 의미해요 성공했습니다.
Drumroll, please.
드럼롤 주세요.
Three, two, one.
셋, 둘, 하나.
Yes!
예!
Garbage!
쓰레기!
The H.I.C. is a bona fide success!
H.I.C. 진정한 성공이다!
H.I.C.! H.I.C.! H.I.C.!
H.I.C.! H.I.C.! H.I.C.!
Yes!
예!
El's waiting for me to pick her up after school.
엘이 날 기다리고 있어 학교 끝나고 데리러 가려고.
Then we can all meet up at the arcade to talk about the new D&D campaign.
그럼 우리 모두 아케이드에서 만나자 새로운 D&D 캠페인에 대해 이야기하려고 합니다.
She'll be happy to know things are finally back to normal.
그녀는 알게 되면 기뻐할 거예요 마침내 모든 것이 정상으로 돌아왔습니다.
Actually, I'll meet you guys at the arcade later.
사실은 내가 너희들을 만나러 갈게 나중에 아케이드에서.
I have this, uh, side quest thing I gotta do.
나 이거 갖고 있어, 어, 사이드 퀘스트 내가 해야 할 일.
- Side quest? Right. - Dude.
- 사이드 퀘스트요? 오른쪽. - 녀석.
You can't even look us in the eye right now.
넌 우리 눈도 똑바로 쳐다볼 수 없어 지금 당장.
Okay, now you gotta tell us what's going on.
알았어, 이제 우리한테 말해야 해 무슨 일이야.
Nope, nuh-uh, never in one million years.
아뇨, 아뇨, 백만 년 동안은 절대요.
Literally, saved by the bell.
말 그대로 벨에 의해 저장되었습니다.
Nikki, where have you been? We haven't seen you since the cabin.
니키, 어디 있었어? 우리는 오두막 이후로 당신을 보지 못했습니다.
Sorry. It was getting late,
죄송합니다. 점점 늦어지고 있었어
and my mom needed to talk to me about something, so...
그리고 우리 엄마는 필요했어 나한테 뭔가 얘기를 좀 하려고...
Well, you missed some pretty big headlines.
글쎄, 당신은 놓쳤어요 꽤 큰 헤드라인이 있어요.
The H.I.C. has officially closed the case,
H.I.C. 공식적으로 사건을 종결했습니다.
which means my D&D game is still on track for the snowstorm.
그건 내 D&D 게임이 아직 제대로 진행 중이라는 뜻이에요 눈보라를 위해.
Wait. "Your D&D game"?
기다리다. "당신의 D&D 게임"?
Don't you think we should discuss it with the party
당신은 생각하지 않는가? 파티와 논의해야 해
before inviting her into the game?
그녀를 게임에 초대하기 전에?
I can make the call. I'm the DM.
전화를 걸 수 있어요. 저는 DM입니다.
Hey, Nikki!
안녕, 니키!
I'll catch you later, Zombie Boy.
나중에 잡을게, 좀비보이.
- Wait. I wanna talk to you. - Yeah?
- 기다리다. 나는 당신과 이야기하고 싶습니다. - 응?
Well, I'm not so sure Wheeler would be cool with that.
글쎄요, 잘 모르겠어요 휠러는 그러면 좋을 것 같아요.
You didn't even ask me first.
나한테 먼저 물어보지도 않았잖아.
So? I can make my own decisions.
그래서? 나는 스스로 결정을 내릴 수 있습니다.
Wait, Nikki!
잠깐, 니키!
- Look, I just think-- - Could you give me a second?
- 내 생각엔-- - 잠시만 시간을 내주실 수 있나요?
DMing is a lot to take on, and--
DMing은 해야 할 일이 많고--
Nikki, hang on!
니키, 잠깐만요!
- Will! - Wait.
- 할 것이다! - 기다리다.
Will!
할 것이다!
What did you do that for?
무엇 때문에 그런 짓을 한 거야?
Okay, which one of you knuckleheads pulled the fire alarm?
좋아, 너희 중 너클헤드 중 누구야? 화재 경보기를 켰나요?
I have zero clue, Coach.
전혀 모르겠어요, 코치님.
I never expected to hear Will, Mike, and "detention" in the same sentence.
윌, 마이크의 말을 들을 줄은 전혀 예상하지 못했습니다. 같은 문장에 "구금"이 포함되어 있습니다.
It was just a matter of time before those good boys went bad.
시간문제였을 뿐이야 그 좋은 소년들이 나빠지기 전에.
I don't know which one did it,
누가 그랬는지 모르겠어요
but I owe them big time for getting me out of my math test.
하지만 난 그들에게 큰 빚을 졌어 나를 수학 시험에서 떨어뜨려줘서.
Hey! Henderson!
여기요! 헨더슨!
We doing this or what?
우리 이거 하는 거야, 아니면 뭐 하는 거야?
Let's go, popcorn head!
가자, 팝콘 머리!
Wait. This is your side quest?
기다리다. 이게 당신의 사이드 퀘스트인가요?
Yes, all right.
응, 알았어.
My mom is mad that I gave my vest away, so I'm going to Rosario's to get it back.
엄마는 내가 조끼를 줬다고 화를 내셨고, 그래서 나는 그것을 돌려받기 위해 로사리오의 집에 갈 예정이다.
That's all, okay?
그게 다야, 알았지?
Whatever you say.
당신이 무엇을 말하든.
Enough chit-chat! We're wasting daylight! Hyah!
잡담은 그만! 우리는 일광을 낭비하고 있습니다! 히아!
I'm going! I'm going!
나는 간다! 나는 간다!
Bye! Have a good break!
안녕! 좋은 휴식을 취하세요!
Welcome to detention, donkeys.
구금에 오신 것을 환영합니다, 당나귀들.
Okay, let's see who we got.
좋아요, 누구인지 봅시다.
- Baxter! - Sir! Present, sir!
- 백스터! - 선생님! 선물하세요!
You're the new biology teacher's kid?
당신은 새로 온 생물학 선생님의 아이인가요?
Yeah.
응.
She must be so proud.
그녀는 정말 자랑스러워 할 것입니다.
Celebrity alert! It's Zombie Byers!
연예인 주의! 좀비 바이어스입니다!
I'm keeping an eye on you.
나는 당신을 감시하고 있습니다.
Can't go missing on my watch.
내 시계에서 누락될 수는 없습니다.
And Mr. Wheeler is here too.
그리고 휠러 씨도 여기에 왔어요.
Shouldn't you be building model rockets instead of pulling fire alarms?
모형 로켓을 만들어야 하지 않겠습니까? 화재 경보기를 울리는 대신?
And it just wouldn't be detention without Charlie Dandridge,
그리고 그것은 단지 구금이 아닐 것입니다 Charlie Dandridge 없이
the poster child for underachievers.
저성취자들을 위한 포스터 아이.
You know the drill.
당신은 훈련을 알고 있습니다.
You'll get it back after detention.
구금 후에 돌려받을 수 있습니다.
For the next hour, there will be no talking, no laughing, no getting up.
다음 시간 동안은 말도 안 하고, 웃지도 말고, 일어나지도 마세요.
And your time starts...
그리고 당신의 시간이 시작됩니다...
now.
지금.
Ugh!
윽!
Ugh! How long is detention anyway?
윽! 어쨌든 구금 기간은 얼마나 되나요?
It's no fun beating Will's Galaga score if he's not there to witness it.
Will의 Galaga 점수를 이기는 것은 재미가 없습니다. 그가 그것을 목격하기 위해 거기에 없다면.
Help!
돕다!
Somebody help!
누군가 도와주세요!
Hey, kid! What's wrong?
이봐, 꼬마야! 무슨 일이야?
My brother's gonna kill me.
내 동생이 날 죽일 ​​거예요.
I dropped his ball, and it bounced right into the tunnel.
나는 그의 공을 떨어뜨렸다. 그리고 그것은 바로 터널 속으로 튕겨져 나갔습니다.
I'm too scared to go get it because I keep hearing things in there.
가서 사러 가기엔 너무 무서워 왜냐면 거기에서 계속 뭔가가 들리거든요.
Tough choice. Nice, warm arcade or icy, stinky sewer.
힘든 선택. 멋지고 따뜻한 아케이드 또는 차갑고 냄새나는 하수구.
Sometimes it stinks to be a hero.
때로는 영웅이 되는 것이 악취가 날 때도 있습니다.
You're going the wrong way, doofus. Your sense of direction sucks.
넌 잘못된 길로 가고 있어, 멍청아. 방향 감각이 형편없어요.
You know what? You've hated me ever since third grade,
그거 알아? 넌 3학년 때부터 나를 미워했지,
and I don't understand why.
왜 그런지 이해가 안 돼요.
Maybe it's because you're a bully
아마도 당신이 깡패이기 때문일 수도 있어요
who threw punch on my new dress at Lindsay Molnar's birthday party.
누가 내 새 드레스에 펀치를 던졌나요? Lindsay Molnar의 생일 파티에서.
That wasn't on purpose.
일부러 그런 건 아니었어요.
Stupid Ian Lee bumped into me.
멍청한 이안이 나한테 부딪혔어.
Would a bully have a dent here from a malicious seesaw incident?
깡패가 여기에 움푹 들어간 곳이 있습니까? 악의적인 시소 사건 때문인가요?
No. Maybe you're the bully.
아뇨. 어쩌면 당신이 깡패일 수도 있어요.
Would a bully have a bald patch
깡패에게 대머리가 생기나요
from being dragged by her ponytail by the pep squad?
그녀의 포니테일에 끌려가서 응원단 때문에?
Jeez.
이런.
Hey. If we knew we had this much in common when we were little,
여기요. 우리가 이만큼 공통점이 있다는 걸 알았더라면 우리가 어렸을 때
do you think we'd have been, I don't know, friends?
우리가 그랬을 거라고 생각하시나요? 모르겠어요, 친구들?
No way. Especially not with your stupid hair.
안 돼요. 특히 당신의 멍청한 머리카락은 그렇지 않습니다.
Then would you settle for a truce?
그러면 휴전을 하시겠습니까?
Whatever.
무엇이든.
Whoa! Are you okay?
와! 괜찮으세요?
Ever since that pie contest, I haven't been able to sleep.
그 파이 대회 이후로, 나는 잠을 잘 수가 없었다.
When I close my eyes, I keep seeing this image.
눈을 감으면, 이 이미지가 계속 보이네요.
You know what? Never mind.
그거 알아? 괜찮아요.
Oh, no, no, no. You can't start a mysterious story like that
아, 아냐, 아냐, 아냐. 시작할 수 없습니다 그런 신비한 이야기
and then just bail.
그리고 그냥 보석금을 내세요.
It's these flashes of a blurry X with a floating red light above it.
이건 흐릿한 X의 깜박임이에요 그 위에 떠다니는 빨간 불빛과 함께.
Just like Charlie. I knew there was something more going on.
찰리처럼. 나는 알고 있었다 뭔가 더 벌어지고 있는 일이 있었다.
Red light. Red light.
빨간불. 빨간불.
Did it look like that?
그렇게 보였나요?
Sort of.
일종의.
But not really.
하지만 실제로는 그렇지 않습니다.
It wasn't just a light.
그것은 단순한 빛이 아니었습니다.
There were trees, branches
나무와 가지가 있었어요
reaching up from below like... fingers.
손가락처럼 아래에서 위로 뻗어요.
I know this sounds crazy,
말도 안 되는 소리인 거 알아요,
but if we can find where you saw this light,
하지만 우리가 찾을 수 있다면 어디서 이 빛을 봤는지,
maybe we can understand why.
어쩌면 우리는 그 이유를 이해할 수 있을지도 모릅니다.
Come on, I'm begging you.
어서, 부탁해요.
I'll owe you big time. Please, please, please.
나는 당신에게 큰 빚을 지게 될 것입니다. 제발, 제발, 제발.
Fine, I'll help.
좋아요, 제가 도와드릴게요.
But only for like an hour. She-Ra starts at 4:30.
하지만 한 시간 정도만요. 쉬라는 4시 30분에 시작합니다.
Yes!
예!
For the honor of Grayskull!
그레이스컬의 명예를 위하여!
All right, rejects. I gotta go make the rounds.
알았어, 거절해. 나는 순회하러 가야 해.
Don't move an inch.
1인치도 움직이지 마세요.
Hey, I'm sorry I landed us in here. I just wanted to talk.
이봐, 우리를 여기까지 데려다줘서 미안해. 그냥 얘기하고 싶었어요.
Hey, chump. You wanna arm wrestle?
이봐, 멍청아. 팔씨름 할래?
You against me?
나한테 반대하는 거야?
Bring it on.
그것을 가져와.
We're still in the wrong spot.
우리는 여전히 잘못된 위치에 있습니다.
It's okay. Let's just keep looking for the right one.
괜찮아요. 계속해서 올바른 것을 찾아봅시다.
We can barely see anything. Time to call it, detective. Let's go.
우리는 거의 아무것도 볼 수 없습니다. 이제 전화할 시간이에요, 형사님. 갑시다.
It just doesn't make sense.
그것은 단지 이해가 되지 않습니다.
If you saw this light, and Charlie saw this light,
이 빛을 봤다면, 그리고 Charlie는 이 빛을 보았습니다
why would you be having the same dream?
왜 같은 꿈을 꾸고 있는 걸까요?
Hey, Earth to Dustin. It's a quarter to She-Ra. Time to go.
안녕, 지구에서 더스틴까지. She-Ra까지 15분 남았습니다. 이제 갈 시간입니다.
She-Ra. That's right!
쉬라. 좋아요!
Adora and her friends, every week, they wage battle against the...
아도라와 그녀의 친구들은 매주 그들은...
Horde Troopers.
호드 기병.
Right.
오른쪽.
But they aren't Adora's biggest enemy. Her main enemy is...
하지만 그들은 아도라의 가장 큰 적이 아닙니다. 그녀의 주요 적은...
Hordak.
호르닥.
Who's sitting in the Fright Zone,
공포지대에 누가 앉아 있는지,
sending his minions out to do the dirty work for him.
그의 부하들을 내보내다 그를 위해 더러운 일을 하려고요.
Maybe that's what's happening here.
아마도 그것이 여기서 일어나고 있는 것일 수도 있습니다.
Which means there must be a bigger enemy out there,
즉 밖에 더 큰 적이 있는 게 틀림없어,
some sort of leader.
일종의 리더.
A queen.
여왕.
You got frostbite of the brain.
당신은 뇌에 동상이 걸렸습니다.
Let's hit the road.
길을 떠나자.
You all right, dude?
괜찮아 친구?
Remember that article we saw back at The Weekly Watcher?
우리가 본 기사를 기억해 보세요 주간 감시자로 돌아왔나요?
"Sewer Serpent Strikes Again"?
"하수구 뱀이 다시 공격한다"?
I think this is the sewer.
여기가 하수구인 것 같아요.
Look!
바라보다!
There's the ball.
공이 있습니다.
What, are you okay?
뭐, 괜찮아?
Gross! I stepped in a puddle.
역겨운! 나는 웅덩이에 발을 디뎠다.
Dude, I thought something happened!
친구, 무슨 일이 일어난 줄 알았어!
Something did happen!
무슨 일이 일어났어요!
I ruined my new sneakers!
새 운동화를 망쳤어요!
My mom's gonna kill me!
엄마가 날 죽일 ​​거야!
Hey. Check it out.
여기요. 확인해 보세요.
Come on!
어서 해봐요!
Run!
달리다!
Lucas!
루카스!
The storm has come earlier than expected and is now far larger,
폭풍이 더 일찍 왔어요 예상보다 훨씬 커졌습니다.
barreling towards Roane County at an unprecedented rate.
로안 카운티를 향해 질주하고 있습니다. 전례 없는 속도로.
Experts are urging anyone in the storm's path...
전문가들의 촉구 폭풍의 길에 있는 사람...
Mike. Mike, are you there?
마이크. 마이크, 거기 있어?
Ha-ha! Boom! The undefeated queen of detention.
하하! 팔! 무패의 구금 여왕.
Best two out of three.
3개 중 2개가 가장 좋습니다.
Two out of three?
3명 중 2명?
We're at, like, nine out of ten, dude.
우린 10점 만점에 9점이에요, 친구.
I guess your new pal likes hanging around jerks.
네 새 친구가 좋아하는 것 같아 바보들 주위에 매달려 있습니다.
Hey, I'm sorry I got us stuck in detention,
저기, 미안해요 우리를 구금시켰어요
but you can't be mad at me forever.
하지만 나에게 영원히 화를 낼 수는 없어요.
'Cause you were trying to impress Nikki?
니키에게 좋은 인상을 주려고 했기 때문에?
Look, I know she's a little--
보세요, 그 사람이 좀--
Okay, she's a lot, but I like her, and so does everyone else.
좋아요, 그녀는 많아요 하지만 나는 그녀를 좋아하고 다른 사람들도 마찬가지입니다.
Doesn't matter. I promised El I'd see her after school,
상관없어요. 엘에게 방과후에 만나기로 약속했어요
but I'm stuck here, and my walkie's in my locker.
하지만 난 여기 갇혀버렸어 그리고 내 무전기는 내 사물함에 있어요.
Then why are you sulking?
그럼 왜 삐죽거리는 거야?
- Let me go! - Let's go get your walkie.
- 놔줘! - 무전기를 가지러 가자.
We can't! Coach will--
우리는 할 수 없습니다! 코치가--
What? Give us detention? We're already here, dude.
무엇? 우리를 구금하라고요? 우리는 이미 여기에 있어요, 친구.
Why do you suddenly care now?
이제 갑자기 왜 신경 쓰이나요?
Maybe because El saved my life, like, 50 times,
어쩌면 엘이 내 생명을 구했기 때문에, 50번 정도,
and I'd like to do her a solid.
그리고 나는 그녀에게 확실한 일을 하고 싶습니다.
Dandridge, you'll stand lookout.
댄드리지, 네가 지켜보게 될 거야.
What's in it for me?
나에게 무엇이 들어있나요?
Uh, the sweet, sweet sounds of X-Ray Spex.
어, X-Ray Spex의 달콤하고 감미로운 소리.
I'll even make you a copy of the tape when we're out of here. What do you say?
테이프 복사도 해줄게 우리가 여기서 나갈 때. 당신은 무엇을 말합니까?
Deal.
거래.
But if this band sucks, you owe me big.
하지만 이 밴드가 형편없다면 나에게 큰 빚을 진 셈이다.
Well, what do you think?
글쎄, 어떻게 생각하세요?
Okay, under one condition.
좋아요, 한 가지 조건 하에서요.
We get it done before Coach gets back.
코치가 돌아오기 전에 끝내자.
Max!
맥스!
Hang on!
잠깐만요!
It's too strong!
너무 강해요!
Max!
맥스!
Look!
바라보다!
Hey, ugly! Over here!
이봐, 못생겼어! 여기요!
What in the...?
그 안에는...?
- Jeff Nelson?
- 제프 넬슨?
The ceiling!
천장!
I don't get paid enough for this.
나는 이것에 대해 충분한 급여를 받지 못합니다.
Hello?
안녕하세요?
I keep imagining things.
자꾸만 상상이 가네요.
Operation Breaker Breaker is a go!
브레이커 작전 브레이커가 시작됩니다!
You know Will can handle himself, right?
윌이 자기 자신을 잘 감당할 수 있다는 거 아시죠?
Dude, you treat him like he's stepping out of line
야, 네가 그 사람을 대접해 마치 그 사람이 줄을 서고 있는 것 같아
every time he tries to do something new. Between this, his D&D game, and--
그가 새로운 일을 하려고 할 때마다. 그 사이에 그의 D&D 게임과--
You don't know Will like I do. He's been through a lot, and--
당신은 윌이 나처럼 될지 모르죠. 그는 많은 일을 겪었고--
Yeah, and maybe he's sick
응, 어쩌면 그 사람이 아픈지도 몰라
of his best friend looking at him like he's broken.
그를 바라보는 가장 친한 친구의 모습 마치 그가 망가진 것처럼.
You ever think about that?
그것에 대해 생각해 본 적 있나요?
You wanna know a secret?
비밀을 알고 싶나요?
Will's the bravest person I know.
윌은 내가 아는 가장 용감한 사람이에요.
Yeah, I can see that.
네, 알겠습니다.
If you can see that, why have you been blowing him off?
그걸 볼 수 있다면, 왜 그 사람을 날려버린 거야?
Because you don't want me here because I "ruin everything," remember?
당신은 내가 여기 있는 걸 원하지 않으니까요 왜냐하면 내가 "모든 것을 망쳐놨기" 때문이죠, 기억하시나요?
I shouldn't have said that. I'm sorry.
그런 말은 하지 말았어야 했는데. 죄송합니다.
But don't shut Will out because of me.
하지만 나 때문에 윌의 문을 닫지는 마세요.
Believe me, I know how scary it is to let people close to you.
날 믿어, 그게 얼마나 무서운지 알아 당신에게 가까운 사람들을 허용하기 위해.
When you do, that means
그렇게 한다는 것은
the things they do or the things that happen to them,
그들이 하는 일들 또는 그들에게 일어난 일들
they can hurt you.
그들은 당신을 해칠 수 있습니다.
But those people can help you too. They can be awesome.
하지만 그 사람들도 당신을 도울 수 있습니다. 그들은 굉장할 수 있습니다.
You just have to let them.
당신은 단지 그들을 허용해야합니다.
Maybe we should both take a page out of Will's book.
어쩌면 우리 둘 다 해야 할지도 몰라 윌의 책에서 한 페이지를 꺼내세요.
And be brave.
그리고 용기를 가지세요.
Are y'all coming or what? Chop-chop!
다들 오시나요? 아니면 뭐요? 찹찹!
Jeff! Come on, man, wake up!
제프! 어서, 일어나!
- Jeff! - Gah!
- 제프! - 가!
What the...?
무슨...?
Sinclair?
싱클레어?
Where am I?
나는 어디에 있습니까?
Maybe just have a seat for a second.
잠시만 자리에 앉아 계실 수도 있습니다.
Do you remember what happened?
무슨 일이 일어났는지 기억하시나요?
It's a blur. Like a crazy dream.
그것은 흐릿하다. 미친 꿈처럼.
- Blinking red lights? - Yeah.
- 빨간불이 깜박이나요? - 응.
But also, there was this urge.
그런데 이런 충동도 있었어요.
Really strong. Like an... instinct.
정말 강해요. 마치... 본능처럼 말이죠.
What kind of instinct?
어떤 종류의 본능?
To hunt. I had the scent of something.
사냥하다. 뭔가 냄새가 나더라구요.
Prey.
먹이.
Not close. Maybe a mile and a half that way.
가깝지 않습니다. 아마 저쪽으로 1.5마일 정도는 될 것 같아요.
I needed to track it down, bring it back, here.
추적해야 했는데, 다시 가져와, 여기.
But why?
그런데 왜?
I don't remember, okay? Get out of my face!
기억이 안 나네요. 그렇죠? 내 얼굴에서 나가!
We only killed one of these things,
우리는 이 중 하나만 죽였습니다.
which means the other three are still out there, hunting.
이것은 나머지 세 개를 의미합니다 아직도 밖에서 사냥을 하고 있어요.
Then we better warn everyone.
그렇다면 모두에게 경고하는 것이 좋을 것 같습니다.
This ain't over yet.
아직 끝나지 않았습니다.
Huh?
뭐?
You feeling okay, Coach?
기분 괜찮으세요, 코치님?
Guys?
얘들아?
I don't think that's Coach.
코치는 아닌 것 같아요.